{
  "qns1":{
    "question": "Are all snakes poisonous?",
    "correct_answer": "No",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Yes",
      "Maybe",
      "I don't know"
    ]
  },
  "qns2":{
    "question": "What is the name of the big animal that has black and white stripes?",
    "correct_answer": "Zebra",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Cheetah",
      "Lion",
      "Deer"
    ]
  },
  "qns3":{
    "question": "What does a caterpillar turn into?",
    "correct_answer": "Butterfly",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Dragonfly",
      "Bee",
      "Ladybug"
    ]
  },
  "qns4":{
    "question": "Do camels store water in their humps?",
    "correct_answer": "No",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Yes",
      "Maybe",
      "I don't know"
    ]
  },
  "qns5":{
    "question": "Which country do wallabies come from?",
    "correct_answer": "Australia",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Indonesia",
      "South Africa",
      "New Zealand"
    ]
  },
  "qns6":{
    "question": "What do tadpoles turn into?",
    "correct_answer": "Frogs",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Fishes",
      "Toads",
      "Water scorpions"
    ]
  },
  "qns7":{
    "question": "What is the name of baby kangaroos?",
    "correct_answer": "Joey",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Chloe",
      "Many",
      "Celine"
    ]
  },
  "qns8":{
    "question": "Can an ostrich fly?",
    "correct_answer": "No",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Yes",
      "Maybe",
      "I don't know"
    ]
  },
  "qns9":{
    "question": "How many legs does an octopus have?",
    "correct_answer": "8",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "12",
      "20",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  "qns10":{
    "question": "How many pairs of wings do bees have?",
    "correct_answer": "2",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "4",
      "6",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  "qns11":{
    "question": "What is a doe",
    "correct_answer": "Female Deer",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Deer",
      "Male Deer",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  "qns12":{
    "question": "What type of animal is an Orca?",
    "correct_answer": "Dolphin",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Whale",
      "Shark",
      "Manta"
    ]
  },
  "qns13":{
    "question": "What is a group of lions called?",
    "correct_answer": "Pride",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Strong",
      "Joy",
      "Fearless"
    ]
  },
  "qns14":{
    "question": "What is the name of baby lions?",
    "correct_answer": "Cub",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Cup",
      "Cut",
      "Cue"
    ]
  },
  "qns15":{
    "question": "How does a male lion advertise its territory?",
    "correct_answer": "Roar and spray urine",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Roar",
      "Spray urine",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  "qns16":{
    "question": "What is the lifespan of a lioness?",
    "correct_answer": "16 Years",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "20 Years",
      "12 Years",
      "14 Years"
    ]
  },
  "qns17":{
    "question": "What animal is called a kid?",
    "correct_answer": "Baby Goat",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Baby Horse",
      "Baby Cow",
      "Baby Rabbit"
    ]
  },
  "qns18":{
    "question": "What is the largest mammal in the world?",
    "correct_answer": "Whale",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Bear",
      "Ostrich",
      "Zebra"
    ]
  },
  "qns19":{
    "question": "Which animal is the tallest in the world?",
    "correct_answer": "Giraffe",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Fox",
      "Lion",
      "Frog"
    ]
  },
  "qns20":{
    "question": "What is Panda’s favourite food?",
    "correct_answer": "Bamboo",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Meat",
      "Fruits",
      "Fish"
    ]
  },
  "qns21":{
    "question": "How many bones do sharks have?",
    "correct_answer": "0",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "236",
      "1000",
      "735"
    ]
  },
  "qns22":{
    "question": "What is the slowest animal in the world?",
    "correct_answer": "Three-toed sloth",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Panda",
      "Turtle",
      "Koala Bear"
    ]
  },
  "qns23":{
    "question": "A snail can sleep for how many years?",
    "correct_answer": "3",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  "qns24":{
    "question": "Which animal never sleeps?",
    "correct_answer": "Bullfrog",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Shark",
      "Elephant",
      "Dolphin"
    ]
  },
  "qns25":{
    "question": "What is a baby fox called?",
    "correct_answer": "Kit",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Kitty",
      "Kid",
      "Kite"
    ]
  },
  "qns26":{
    "question": "Which animal does not drink water?",
    "correct_answer": "Kangaroo rat",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tortoise",
      "Snakes",
      "Frogs"
    ]
  },
  "qns27":{
    "question": "Which animal has the longest lifespan?",
    "correct_answer": "Arctic Whale",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Shark",
      "Penguin",
      "Elephant"
    ]
  },
  "qns28":{
    "question": "How many legs does a lobster have?",
    "correct_answer": "10",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  "qns29":{
    "question": "What kind of animal is a komodo dragon?",
    "correct_answer": "Lizard",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Snakes",
      "Frog",
      "Chameleon"
    ]
  },
  "qns30":{
    "question": "Which animal has stripes?",
    "correct_answer": "Zebra",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Lion",
      "Hippopotamus",
      "Penguin"
    ]
  },
  "qns31":{
    "question": "What color does a penguin have?",
    "correct_answer": "All of the above",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Yellow",
      "Black",
      "White"
    ]
  },
  "qns32":{
    "question": "Which animal is smaller than you?",
    "correct_answer": "Rabbit",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Pony",
      "Horse",
      "Cow"
    ]
  },
  "qns33":{
    "question": "Which animal is bigger than you?",
    "correct_answer": "Giraffe",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Panda",
      "Sea Lion",
      "Fox"
    ]
  },
  "qns34":{
    "question": "Which animal has a mane?",
    "correct_answer": "Lion",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Bear",
      "Cheetah",
      "Panda"
    ]
  },
  "qns35":{
    "question": "Which animal has spots on it?",
    "correct_answer": "Leopard",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Buffalo",
      "Snake",
      "Kangaroo"
    ]
  },
  "qns36":{
    "question": "Which animal has more than 4 colors?",
    "correct_answer": "Panther Chameleon",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Snake",
      "Frog",
      "Lobster"
    ]
  },
  "qns37":{
    "question": "Which animal has scales?",
    "correct_answer": "Snake",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Sea Lion",
      "Elephant",
      "Rabbit"
    ]
  },
  "qns38":{
    "question": "Which animal has a shell on it?",
    "correct_answer": "Giant Tortoise",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Crocodile",
      "Bear",
      "White Tiger"
    ]
  },
  "qns39":{
    "question": "Which animal swings from trees to trees?",
    "correct_answer": "Monkey",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Koala Bear",
      "Three-toed sloth",
      "Malayan Flying Fox"
    ]
  },
  "qns40":{
    "question": "What is the lifespan of a tortoise?",
    "correct_answer": "100 years and above",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "100 years",
      "100 years and below",
      "50 years"
    ]
  },
  "qns41":{
    "question": "What is the lifespan of a California sea lion?",
    "correct_answer": "30 Years",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "40 Years",
      "20 Years",
      "10 Years"
    ]
  },
  "qns42":{
    "question": "Which mammal has the most powerful bite in the world?",
    "correct_answer": "Hippopotamus",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "White Rhinoceros",
      "Crocodile",
      ""
    ]
  },
  "qns43":{
    "question": "Which animal did the Guinness Book of World Records name as the most fearless animal?",
    "correct_answer": "Honey Badger",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Leopard",
      "Cheetah",
      "Lion"
    ]
  },
  "qns44":{
    "question": "Lemurs are only native to one country, which one is it?",
    "correct_answer": "Madagascar",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Australia",
      "Indonesia",
      "Egypt"
    ]
  },
  "qns45":{
    "question": "Which large marine mammals are sometimes known as sea cows?",
    "correct_answer": "Manatees",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Hippopotamus",
      "White Rhinoceros",
      "Sea Lion"
    ]
  },
  "qns46":{
    "question": "Where is the habitat of a small-clawed otter?",
    "correct_answer": "Freshwater swamps",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Sandy Beaches",
      "Coastal waters",
      "Shorelines"
    ]
  },
  "qns47":{
    "question": "Which animal’s tail is longer than its body?",
    "correct_answer": "Ring-tailed Lemur",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Snake",
      "Giraffe",
      "Chameleon"
    ]
  },
  "qns48":{
    "question": "Which reptile has the strongest bite force?",
    "correct_answer": "Estuarine Crocodile",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "King Cobra",
      "Komodo Dragon",
      "Indian Gharial"
    ]
  },
  "qns49":{
    "question": "Which animal likes mud spa to cool themselves?",
    "correct_answer": "White Rhinoceros",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Hippopotamus",
      "Crocodile",
      "Cow"
    ]
  },
  "qns50":{
    "question": "What does a Malayan flying fox have on a diet?",
    "correct_answer": "Pollen",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Flower",
      "Fruits",
      "Vegetables"
    ]
  }
}
